we did a lot. I know it sounded like four sections when we first started with components,
composables, routing, and state management. But as you know, the meat of today was really just
getting our hands, you know, elbow deep in composables so that when you go back to your
code bases, you're just going to be like, yeah, I'm just going to create one and you're not going
to think twice about it. I think if we, if that's where people are feeling and then you got to
get your hands on with some of those more, it's kind of call it advanced composition design patterns
where there are more edge cases, but again, as software architect, we do need to understand how
to navigate those things. And so, you know, those are things that we touched on as well. And then
a lot of you got to play with file base routing, it seems for the first time which is fun.
Yeah, so that's like, for me, it's such a big DX improvement. And then, finally, of course, you know,
we kind of wrapped it up to show that like, all our work with composables really is not so far
from the state management library we already have, that the official one we have for view. So again,
I have met people at other workshops who they're like, you know, opinions great, but we decided
to hand roll our own, we have our type safe, you know, we have our document away of doing it.
And then I can't stress enough. If that works for you, you know, like, go for it.
Just know that, you know, these, these prevole options are still very suitable and worth your time.
Should you choose to use it? Just a comment in the chat that this is a very informative workshop
and a really great addition to your fundamentals course. Right? I really appreciate that,
but just kind of in terms of other final thoughts. So I just kind of, these are the things that we
covered. Lots of different techniques within them. So do not sell yourself short of the things we did.
So of course, the next question is now you've just finished the intermediate workshop. What is next?
And so to you, I present in this comic, I hate myself. It's where it starts. Their fist combined
says, look, TypeScript. And then, wow, I hate this even more. I kid. Now, the things that TypeScript
I don't know. For me personally, I have a love hate relationship with it. There are times where
I'm like, wow, this is great. It's doing exactly what I want. And then there's other time where the
bill tool is breaking and I'm like, nothing works. I want to chuck all this in the bin. It's, it's,
for me, it's a very much a love hate relationship. That said, it's more I said ingest. I mean,
obviously we're here as a front end workshops, front end masters workshop, but view is ultimately,
I tell this to people all the time. It's a framework about helping to get the craft out of the
ways you can do what's important to you. And once we provided those fundamentals with composition
API now, as we talked about, a lot of the next step really is to just about advancing your skills
as a JavaScript software architect. Because the patterns we're talking about, singletons,
factories, we talked about different ways to share a state, how to keep the modular.
Those are all things that it shared across the fields we do. Regardless of whatever
framework it is that you do. And so there are wonderful, as you know, workshops, or for those
if you are new, wonderful workshops they have here that to kind of take your JavaScript or
Typhoon knowledge further on. So if Typhoon is scary, definitely this is the place to check out.
And then for those who haven't had the joy of doing checking this out, be sure to check out
next. Nux is kind of this wonderful paradise of like DX enhancement that the things you love
about view three, they're like cool. We're going to like just build stuff in that we think has
worked really well. And then you just try it out. So things like the page, like the file based
running that we did, that's built into this. So people who have been using Nux three have had this for
quite some time. It's only recently come to view three as like a separate plugin. They have things
like auto imports on your composables. They have already built in patterns for like how api libraries
can or api fetching can be done. They have their own native use fetch as well because you know we
we built like a very barebones one our own. And then more importantly Nux can handle all the SSR
hydration. You know you want to do some stuff static. You want to do some stuff see it like client
side rendered. It can do all that. And so the hybrid rendering like it makes like like just to show
you like Nux hybrid rendering. Like I don't know if any of you have ever dove into this on your
own but like SSR is a is a rabbit hole. And so what's cool? Like check this out. You can just set
route rules and then tell it which strategy you wanted to use for what page. Yeah it's like cool
pre-render this. Do like still well revalidate on that. I mean the acronyms kind of get all over the
place but you can see here. I mean I don't know I don't know if it gets much easier than that right
when it comes to mixing your renderings strategy for your site especially when a lot of things you
don't need to be constantly re-rendered or not everything needs to be SSR. You know I think in software
development we do have a tendency to like over index on like whatever the hot thing is. And so you know SSR
was the way we always did it and then it's almost like we forgot about it and then it became a
thing again and then everyone's like oh SSR everything it's like you know there's a world where
everything plays together and so this this kind of stuff reminds me that like yeah we can have some
stuff that's pre-rendered which is great. These statically generated other stuff like blog posts right
you don't need that to be generated you know every especially on the client side just generating
one so deployment cash it things like that. And so Nux is phenomenal if you have a chance to play
around with another project and you're starting a new new view project again it can't
speak highly enough of Nux the team is phenomenal. If you're looking for someone to follow Daniel Roe
is the project lead on Nux he is fantastic. And then I'm curious has anyone here heard of Viet Press?
Yay okay great for those who haven't this is the successor to Viet Press if you didn't hear
about that one and essentially it's just a static site generator that creates a dock site
that looks just like Viet Press.dev. It basically looks like this except everything is configured
via Markdown and so like if you're getting started you can see here the home page is just like you
add the title description some theme config stuff and then you get all this navigation you get
theming you get the ability to have like next page like it's basically all marked out but
the back end of it will statically generate for you and then it even uses view underneath the
hood for theming and so there's actually a lot of open source projects use this these days and
then they're not even view related they just wanted to create a dock site and Viet Press is incredibly
easy like you start up the starter project you add some Markdown files while it works it's
pretty great so shout out to Viet Press as well for those looking for like hey I want to spin up like a
little internal dock site for my team this is great this is like I can't this is phenomenal for that kind
of thing and people use it at scale like I think pinia all the docks you see in the view I think
we all use Viet Press. The previous the whole like view next. I think nuts does have nuts docks
though so that's where I hesitate so it's a little it's similar but yeah but nonetheless Viet Press
on its own impressive and nuts docks I guess honorage honorable mention to them as well
I'm having the chance to use them as much but they also create great stuff but yeah you can see
five base routing yeah how's our congratulations you ought to be proud of your sales
I really appreciate everyone spending the time with me today and I was been a long day but again
with all your feedback and questions and stuff it really makes this a pleasurable experience so
thanks everyone for coming by